How was the content of the lectures?
讲课的内容是什么？
Was it easy for you?
对你来说简单吗？
I didn't really have many problems understanding lectures.
我在理解课程上没有什么问题。
The content was very similar to what I'd studied before.
学习的内容和我之间学的很像。
And what about the lecturers themselves?
老师怎么样？
Are they essentially the same as lecturers in your country?
他们在本质上和你的国家的老师一样吗？
Well actually,no.Here,they're much easier to approach.
事实上不是这样。这里的老师很容易接近。
After every lecture you can go and ask them something you didn't understand.
每节课后，你都能找他们问你不懂的问题，
Or you can make an appointment and talk to them about anything in the course.
或者你可以预约与他们讨论课上的任何事。
Maybe you found them different because you're a more mature student now,
也许你发觉他们不同是因为你现在更成熟了，
whereas when you were studying in your country you were younger and not so assertive.
当你在你的国家上学时，你还很年轻，观点不是很明确。
No,I don't think that's the difference.
不，我不认为这是区别。
Most of the students here do it.
这里的很多学生都这么做。
In my faculty,they all seem to make appointments - usually to talk about something in the course that's worrying them,
在我的系里，他们似乎都会预约，通常谈论课上让他们烦恼的问题，
but sometimes just about something that might really interest them, something they might want to speciallse in.
但是有时谈论的只是他们感兴趣的话题，一些让他们想要专门从事的事情。
The lecturers must set aside certain times every week when they're available for students.
老师必须每周留出一定的时间给学生。
That's good to hear.
这很好。